

Harry

Product Designer

★ Machine Mac

4 +9509428310392

Portfolio Website

I am digital product designers with **5 years experiences** on digital product development. And my goal since my teenage is to make digital products to **help people's life more easier and efficient**. My Slogan is **"I Design Products With Love"**.

Career History

Founder @ Design Matters May 2022 - Present

- Goal is to educate and correct the design process of the local designers so that we, the designers
 can generate user-centered, useful and emotionally triggered design that people really love.
- Currently, we started mentorship session where we guide more than 50 local designers from local companies like BIM AYA Pay, KBZ, Beyond Limit and other companies at the moment.
- Also we planned to host biggest UX Event in Myanmar on October 7 and 8 of 2023 with 20
 Designer Speakers. And more than 300 Designers are registered to attend and still counting.

Outcomes • We got big positive reputation in the UXUI Design industry.

Senior UX Designer @ Lexagle October 2022 - April 2023

- I own **obligation management** feature, **public link to streamline contract inquiries**. I collaborate with UI Designers Product Managers and Developers.
- I plan for the UX Debt along with the product team lead in order to trace and fix the UX Debts that happened in the organization.
- I set KPI for the 2 internship(1 UX Researcher and 1 DesignOps) for their growth plan and the process in our design team.

Outcomes • Features are delivered to developers

UX Designer @ Treedots November 2021 - October 2022

- I took **ownership on Supplier Portal for B2B Business Arm** by collaborating together with Product Managers and Developers. Features that I design includes Sales Management, Order Management, Inventory Management, Dispute Management and so on.
- I also assist our Team Lead in **building a remote-friendly work environment** by leading activities like Good Vibe Fridays, fostering a strong Team.
- I also took part in hiring designers for the team along with the team lead. And hire 2 designers who are still working for that company.
- I volunteered in addressing UX Debts in the system and solve by conducting user research, creating sitemaps, user flows, prototypes, design systems and usability testings, setting UX Metrics.

Outcomes

- MVP with 7 Features into the market.
- Successfully build remote friendly and collaborative and Tracking UX Debt Plan impacting the team productivity.

Product Designer @ Nexlabs September 2020 - November 2021

 I collaborated with the design team, developers and business analysts in order to create design for diverse industries requested by clients. I design mobile and website products for FinTech, HealthTech, Entertainment and Community Based Non Profit Organizations.

Outcomes: More than 5 digital products including mobile application, website and web applications are delivered into the market.

UI/UX Designer @ Adventsoft October 2022 - April 2023

I transaction from a Software Engineer to UI/UX Designer. My main responsibility is to design
mobile and web products for FinTech, Telehealth, E Commerce, Ride Hailing Platform, Insurances
and Education Industries.

Outcomes • More than 10 digital products are completely hand-over to the developer

Internship @ Acroquest October 2022 - April 2023

• During the final year of my university, I worked as an Internship. My responsibility is to create web application with Spring Boot.

Outcomes

• I understood how the digital products are developed in the industry and hand on experiences with Software Development Life Cycle.

Educations

Computer Sciences Degree @ University of Computer Studies, Taunggyi 2013 - 2018

• I learn about Computer Science, Human-Computer Interaction, Cyber Security, Software Engineering and Project Management.

Skills

Hard Skills

Wireframing , Rapid Prototyping , Design Research , Affinity Mapping , Workshop Ideation , Project Management , Accessibility , User Research , Design System , UX Debts Management

Soft Skills

Effective Communication , Leadership , Problem Solving , Crictical Thinking, People & Stakeholder Management

Software Engineering Skills

Java, Javascript, Flutter, Spring Boot, Python, Data Sciences, Machine Learning Basic

Certifications

Enterprise Design System - Co Creator (IBM) Enterprise Design System - Practioner (IBM)

Product Management (Great Learning) Introduction To Design Thinking (Great Learning)

Team Essential For AI (Great Learning)

Tools Usage

Design & Documentation Tools

Figma, Figjam, Adobe CC, Sketch, Whimsicals, Notion, Maze, Protopie, Useberry

Communication Tools

· Slack, Microsoft Office, Google Workplace

Utalities Tools

Trello, Moleskine Studio, ChatGPT, Adobe Firefly, Speechify, Mobbin, Dribbble, Behance, Medium, Google Scholar. Google Colab

Community Service

During my Amateur designer year (around 2019), I want the **design community where I can took mentorship session and improving my design skills.** But I can't find the proper one in Myanmar as the fields is not booming yet. I set a goal that when I have the experiences and skillset, I will found the community where local designers can rely on for their career growth.

And on May 2022, me and my colleague designer start founding the Community called "Design Matters" and contributing and having good impact on Myanmar Design Communities in terms of the following statistics.

50+	10+	4
Overall Mentorship Session	My Mentorship Session	Hosted Webinar
66	3 Events	10+
NPS Score on Mentorship Session	We are invited as a guest speaker	Hosted Knowledge Sharing Session
6	2.2K	336
Hosted Bootcamp	Followers On Facebook	Members In Discord Community